let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Through which of the following parts do <b> Fish </b> breathe?",
    answer: "Gill",
    options: [
      "Spiracles",
      "Gill",
      "Lungs",
      "Moist Skin"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following parts give support to the <b> Lungs </b>",
    answer: "Diaphragm",
    options: [
      "Bronchioles",
      "Bronchus",
      "Diaphragm",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the approximate percentage of oxygen in exhaled air?",
    answer: "16%",
    options: [
      "17%",
      "21%",
      "16%",
      "4%"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the incorrect statement for <b> Breathing </b>?",
    answer: "It is a Chemical Change",
    options: [
      "It occur outside the cells",
      "There is no energy released",
      "It is a Chemical Change",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is the red-coloured <b> Protein </b> present in blood cells",
    answer: "Haemoglobin",
    options: [
      "Haemoglobin",
      "Chlorophyll",
      "Vitamin",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },

 {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many molecules of oxygen can combine with <b> Heamoglobin </b> ?",
    answer: "4",
    options: [
      "12",
      "2",
      "8",
      "4"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following <b> Category </b> does frog comes under ?",
    answer: "Amphibians",
    options: [
      "Amphibians",
      "Reptile",
      "Mammal",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "__________ is the process by which undigested food is removed from the body in the form of faeces ?",
    answer: "Egestion",
    options: [
      "Egestion",
      "Digestion",
      "Assimilation",
      "Absorption"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Through which of the following parts does <b> Amoeba </b> do the process of Digestion?",
    answer: "Pseudopodia",
    options: [
      "Food Vocuole",
      "Cyptoplasm",
      "Pseudopodia",
      "Nucleus"
    ]
  },

   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the is the hardest part of the body? ",
    answer: "Enamel",
    options: [
      "Ball-and-socket Bone",
      "Collar Bone",
      "Enamel",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },



];